topikguide.com 2019-11-18

# Privacy Policy | TOPIK GUIDE - The Complete Guide to TOPIK Test

At [TOPIK GUIDE](https://www.topikguide.com/), the privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

 **1\. Log Files**

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

 **2\. Cookies**

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, TOPIK GUIDE has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites. Google, a third party vendor, may use the _DoubleClick DART Cookie_ to serve ads on TOPIK GUIDE. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google’s Content Network Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

 **3\. Private Data**

 **We don’t store any of your sensitive personal data (like your credit card number etc.) except what is necessary to provide you our services (ex: name, email id etc.).** We use reputed third-party payment gateway methods (Paypal, 2Checkout and Gumroad) for payment processing. If you make purchases on our website, we collect certain data about your purchase (such as your name and email ID) as necessary to process your order. You must provide certain payment and billing data directly to our payment processing partners, including your name, credit card information, billing address, and zip code. **For security, TOPIK GUIDE does not collect or store sensitive cardholder data, such as full credit card numbers or card authentication data.** You can contact the payment processors directly  in case of any problem or concern related to payments.

 **4\. Disclosure of your information**

 **TOPIK GUIDE will not use or disclose your personal information without your consent** , except where required or authorised by law, to implement the terms of any agreement we have with you, to assist the lawful investigation of a law enforcement authority, to protect the rights, property or personal safety of another TOPIK GUIDE customer, any member of the public or TOPIK GUIDE, the assets and operations of the business are transferred to another party as a going concern or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

 **5\. Your rights**

We send information, updates and marketing communications from time to time to update you on TOPIK test, Korean language in general or our products. You may elect to stop receiving our emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in such emails.

 **You also have the right to have your information rectified or erased as well as the right to request a copy of your personal information held by us.**

You can exercise your rights by sending an email to info@topikguide.com.

If you withdraw your consent to the use of your personal information for purposes set out in our Privacy Policy, we may not be able to provide you with access to all or parts of our Website.

 **6\. Policy Modifications**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and any amended Privacy Policy will be posted on our Website and notified to you by email, where appropriate. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 17 May 2018 and replaces any other Privacy Policy previously applicable from this date.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@topikguide.com.

Last Updated: May 17, 2018
